《生活大爆炸》前情回顾
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
这只是一点小挫折
This is just a minor setback.
这不是  明白吗
No, it's not, okay?
我已经离家拼搏十年了
I've been out here for, like, ten years.
我依然一无所有
I have nothing to show for it.
你有我啊
Well, you have me.
我的确拥有你
I do have you.
莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德
Leonard Hofstadter,
你愿意娶我吗
will you marry me?
你刚才那一声是在犹豫吗
Did you seriously just say, "Um..."?
-这太过分了  -我明白
- It's an outrage. - I know.
大学的高层觉得他们想干嘛就能干嘛
The university-- they think they can do whatever they want.
我们只能乖乖任由摆布
We just have to sit there and take it.
别老拽着这事不放了  谢尔顿
You need to let it go, Sheldon.
我没日没夜地为他们干活  却落得如此下场
You work tirelessly for someone, and this is what you get.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God!
他们就是让你把年假用掉而已
They're just making you use your vacation days!
可我不想放假
But I don't want a vacation.
我不想轻视你心灵受到的创伤
Okay, listen, I don't mean to diminish what you're going through,
但我现在真的没心思
but I'm a little distracted right now.
又是因为那事啊
Oh, this again?
不就是佩妮求了婚  你没答应嘛
So, Penny proposed, you didn't say yes,
所以现在你天天发愁到底会不会失去她
and now you think you may have lost her love forever.
这破事怎么比得上我被人
How does this compare to me being forced
逼迫放假来得惨啊
to relax for a few days?
-完全比不上  -就是嘛
- It doesn't! - Thank you!
我要去跟佩妮谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to Penny.
我要回家穿上我最舒服的睡衣
I'm going to go inside, put on my coziest pajamas,
蜷在床上看本好书
curl up with a good book
等待这场噩梦的结束
and wait for this nightmare to be over.
佩妮
Penny.
抱歉  情不自禁
Sorry.
抱歉没回你短信
Hey. Look, I'm sorry I didn't text you back.
我只是需要点时间想想
I just needed some time to think.
-没事  -来  进来吧
- Okay. - Here. Come in.
如果你是想要分手  就说出来吧
Look, if you want to break up, just say it.
-莱纳德...  -别别别  我收回那句话
- Leonard... - No, no, no, no. I take it back.
千万别分手  恨我就好  别离开我
Don't say it. Just-just hate me, but stay with me.
反正我爸妈也这样
It worked for my parents.
听我说  我没想要跟你分手
Listen, I don't want to break up with you.
那就好
Oh. O-Okay.
很好  很好
Good, good.
不介意我落两滴男儿泪吧
So, it's cool if I cry a little?
要我就不会这么做
Yeah, I probably wouldn't.
同意
Yeah.
你昨晚的做法是正确的
Look, you did the right thing last night.
我当时脑子不清楚
I was a mess.
当时我因为事业不顺  内心严重受挫
I was just frustrated because my career is going nowhere.
我理解  我也想你知道
Look, I get it, and I want you to know
无论你想做什么事  我都支持你
that I support whatever you want to do.
那就好  因为我在想
Great, because I've been thinking,
如果我真想要演员事业能成功
if I really want this acting thing to work,
我就得身心完全投入
I need to focus all my energy on it.
为了做到真正投入
And to do that,
我决定辞芝士蛋糕工厂的服务员工作
I should quit waitressing at The Cheesecake Factory.
-这是个大改变啊  -我知道
- That-That's a big step. - I know.
所以在你做任何冲动的...
So, you know, before making any rash...
-我已经辞职了  -那我也支持你
- I already quit. - And I support you!
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
生活大爆炸
第七季  第十三集
-好嘛  带我跟你去上班  -不行
- Come on, take me to work with you. - No.
-你在放假  -求你了
- You're on vacation. - Please.
万一今天科学界有重大突破
What if there's a big breakthrough in science today
我却错过无法见证呢
and I'm not there to see it?
你真的觉得你如果不在  科学界能有什么
Do you really think there's gonna be a breakthrough
重大突破吗
without you there to do it?
当然不会有  这是陷阱题
No. I was just tricking you.
再会
Bye.
莱纳德  等等
Leonard, wait!
-带我一起去  -不行
- Take me with you.- No!
-求你了  -就是不行
- Please. - No!
抱歉  我就是要跟着你
Too bad. I'm coming with you.
-谢尔顿  停  -但是...
- Oh, Sheldon, stay! - But...
乖乖待着
I said stay!
我要去上班了
I'm going to work.
不许跟着我
Do not follow me.
斯图尔特
Hey, Stuart.
-你好啊  -抱歉  我吓到你了吗
- Hey. - Sorry. Did I startle you?
没关系  这时间所有客人都会吓到我
Yes, but at this point, pretty much any customer does.
你要买什么
What can I do for you?
我需要你帮个忙
Well, I need a little help.
今早我不小心弄坏了霍华德的一本漫画书
I accidentally destroyed one of Howard's comic books this morning,
所以我想买一本来替换
and I was hoping I could replace it.
发生了什么事
Wow. What happened?
蝙蝠侠被我的烫发棒给虐了
Batman got his ass kicked by my curling iron.
可别把这个秘密告诉谜语人
Well, don't let The Riddler know that.
这是个漫画哏啦
It's a comic book joke.
也可能不是哏吧
Or maybe it's not.
你还有这本书吗
Do you have this one?
这本书市面上很少见了
Uh, well, it's-it's pretty rare.
我需要几天时间找一下
Can you give me a few days to track it down?
我还希望能在华仔下班
Ooh, I was kind of hoping to get it
回家之前就把书换掉
before Howie comes home from work.
干嘛这么着急
Oh. What's the hurry?
他平时就爱念叨
Well, he's always saying
让我用烫发棒的时候多注意点
I should be more careful with my curling iron,
要是让他发现
and it seems like a dangerous precedent
他也有说对的时候就惨了
to let him think he can be right.
我尽力而为吧
Well, I'll do what I can,
但我可不敢打包票一定能找到
but I can't make any promises.
其实我在制药公司工作呢
You know, I do work at a pharmaceutical company.
如果你今天能帮我找到书
If you can make this happen today,
我就能帮你搞点抗焦虑
I can hook you up with anxiety medication,
-和抗抑郁的药  -是吗
- antidepressants. - Really?
那你有这些药吗
Do you have any of these?
鼠脑君  你好吗
Hello, Mr. Rat Brain.
没了身体的其他部分
Not so bitey without the rest of the rat
现在没法咬我了吧
to back us up now, are we?
有人吗
Anybody home?
你俩来干什么
Hey, what brings you guys here?
我们要去吃午饭
Well, we were just on our way to lunch
顺道看看你想不想一起去
and wanted to see if you'd like to join.
为什么
Why?
因为这周谢尔顿不上班
Because Sheldon's not here this week,
你们就觉得我没有别人陪伴了吗
and you don't think I have any other options?
开玩笑的  我拿上包就走
I'm just kidding. I'll get my purse.
艾米  我
Hi, Amy. I... Oh.
抱歉  我不知道你有客人在
I'm sorry. I didn't know you had any company.
没关系
That's okay.
伯特  这是霍华德和拉杰什
Uh, Bert, this is Howard and Rajesh.
这位是Bert
Guys, this is Bert.
-很高兴见到你  -你好
- Hey. Good to see you. - Hey.
我是想过来给你看看
Anyway, I wanted to show you
我们在实验室弄出来的石英晶体
this tourmalinated quartz that we got in the lab.
真漂亮
This is so pretty.
-伯特在地质系工作  -没错
- Bert works for the geology department. - Yeah.
你们知道地质学家和邦·乔飞的共同点是什么吗
You know what, uh, geologists and Bon Jovi have in common?
你们都喜欢石头[摇滚]吗
You're both into rock?
答对了
Yeah.
再见
Well, see ya.
你忘了把石英拿走了
Oh, you forgot your quartz.
没关系
Oh, it's okay.
送给你吧
I want you to have it.
再见
Bye.
他人真好
He's nice.
他对你好是因为他喜欢你
Yeah, he's nice because he likes you.
什么呀  他才不喜欢我呢
What?! No, he doesn't.
他送你一块漂亮的石头
He brought you a pretty rock.
那又怎样  他每天都送我...
So? He does that every day...Oh.
如果你不想吃午饭
You know, if you'd rather skip lunch
而想和你男友伯特在一起  我们完全没意见
and hang out with your boyfriend Bert, it's totally okay.
他才不是我男朋友呢
He's not my boyfriend.
你确定吗  他个高  肤白  人怪
Are you sure? He's tall, pale and awkward.
貌似就是你的菜啊
That sounds like your type.
你这种万年没人爱的家伙也敢来取笑我吗
Should someone as lonely as you really be making fun of me?
没错  霍华德  你成熟点好不好
Yeah, grow up, Howard. God.
我该怎么做呢  我不想伤害他的感情
What do I do? I don't want to hurt his feelings.
也许问题就出在他不知道你名花有主了
Maybe the problem is he thinks you're available.
他知道你在跟谢尔顿谈恋爱吗
Does he know you're dating Sheldon?
好像从没提过这事
I guess it hasn't come up.
看吧
There you go.
那谢尔顿知道你们俩是算在谈恋爱吗
And does Sheldon know you're dating Sheldon?
不好意思  那你又是跟谁在恋爱
I'm sorry. Who are you dating?
就是  把嘴闭上  霍华德
Yeah, knock it off, Howard!
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
你好
Hello.
你没事吧
You okay?
我在上班  你觉得呢
I'm on vacation. What do you think?
那你为什么坐在楼梯上
Why are you sitting in the stairwell?
莱纳德让我待在这
Leonard told me to stay.
真听话  乖孩子[狗狗]
Oh. Well, good boy.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要出去办一堆事
Oh, I have a ton of errands to run.
我得去多洗几张我的大头照
I need to make copies of my headshot,
寄给不同的经济人
send them off to agents
然后去报一门新的表演课
and sign up for a new acting class and...
-祝你忙得开心  -好的
- Well, have fun. - Okay.
-你要不要一起来  -可以吗
- You want to come with me? - Really?
当然可以  走吧  快  乖孩子[狗狗]
Come on, boy. Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
快上车  走
Get in the car. Come on.
谢天谢地
All right, thanks a lot.
首都漫画店有一本
They have one at Capital Comics.
-那太棒了  -才不是
- Oh, that's great. - No, it's not.
我讨厌那地方
I hate that place.
那个店主就是一个混蛋
Guy who owns it is a jerk.
他总爱让我产生强烈的自卑感
He's always making me feel bad about myself.
太糟糕了
Oh, that's terrible.
那家店在哪里
What's the address?
算了  要不我带你去吧
You know, why don't I just take you there?
这样我能确保他不会趁机敲诈
That way, I can make sure he doesn't rip you off.
多谢啦  但我不希望你关门
Oh, thanks, but I don't want you to close up.
你会损失客人的
I mean, won't you lose business?
抱歉  这话太损了
Sorry. That was mean.
-佩妮真的辞掉了服务员的工作吗  -是的
- Penny really quit The Cheesecake Factory? - Yeah.
-那她今天干什么  -我不知道
- So, what is she doing today? - I don't know.
她已经认为我在这方面不支持她
She already thinks I don't support this,
所以如果我打给她  就会像查岗一样
so if I call, it might look like I'm checking up on her.
那你支持她吗
Well, do you support this?
当然支持
Of course I do.
她是一名很棒的女演员
She's a great actress.
她敢冒这个险  真让我感到骄傲
I'm proud she's taking this risk.
你真贴心
That's nice.
你还真信啊  太棒了
You bought that? Great!
我要在忘记怎么演之前  赶快打给佩妮
I got to call her before I forget how I said it.
怎么了
Hi. What's up?
进展如何
Oh, how's it going?
你有没有袭卷好莱坞啊
You taking Hollywood by storm?
其实我现在在芝士蛋糕工厂呢
Actually, I'm at The Cheesecake Factory.
你要回工作啦  那真是太好了
You got your job back. That is great news.
我本来不想多说什么
I didn't want to say anything,
但你这么做才是正确的
but you are making the right choice.
现在就切断自己的经济来源
To plunge yourself into debt right now
-简直就是疯了嘛  -是啊
- would be literally insane. Yeah.
我是来这还工作服的
I'm just returning my uniform.
对了  我支持你哦
And I support you.
在开始接受冥想引导前
Before we begin your guided meditation,
闭上眼
close your eyes
想象自己处于一个平和安详的环境
and picture yourself in a peaceful environment.
好的
Okay.
我处于欧洲核子研究中心的超级对撞机里
I'm inside the CERN super collider.
现在用鼻子轻松地深吸一口气
Now, take a deep, relaxing breath in through your nose.
然后呼气
And let it out.
真是"没想到"啊
Didn't see that coming.
吸气
In.
下一步肯定是...
Let me guess.
呼气
And out.
不然咧  连吸两口气憋死自己吗
What was I gonna do? Two "ins" in a row?
我的柠檬汁呢
Where's my lemonade?
我忘了
I didn't get it.
告别你服务员职业生涯的最佳方式
A fitting swan song to your career as a waitress
就是最后一次忘记我的点单
to forget my order one last time.
你认为我辞职是个错误吗
Do you think quitting my job was a mistake?
你有看到我在喝柠檬汁吗
Do you see me drinking lemonade?
我是说真的
No. I'm serious.
干嘛这么问
Why do you ask?
因为莱纳德刚刚气到我了
Because Leonard just pissed me off.
我辞职是不是特傻啊
Am I being an idiot or not?
不啊  我不这么认为
No, I don't think you are.
真的吗
Really?
达到目标的最好办法就是投入自己
The best way to achieve a goal is to devote 100%
百分之百的时间和精力
of your time and energy to it.
当我决心要成为一个物理学家时
When I decided I was going to be a physicist,
我没有随便找一份工作
I didn't take some other job
好给自己留一条后路
in case it didn't work out.
这决定不容易  因为那年皮尔森老师
Which wasn't easy because there was a lot of pressure
不断对我施压  让我当补粉笔专员
from Ms. Pierson for me to be chalk monitor that year.
谢谢  我需要这样的鼓励
Thank you. I needed to hear that.
为什么莱纳德就是不明白呢
Why can't Leonard understand it?
因为他不像咱俩  佩妮
Because he's not like us, Penny.
我们是梦想家
We're dreamers.
是是  下次再把你留在车里
Yeah, I need to start cracking the window
得留个缝  免得你脑子缺氧了
when I leave you in the car.
你好  伯特
Hello, Bert.
对了  下周在圣塔莫尼卡有个
So, anyway, there's this big, uh, rock and mineral show
大型的岩石矿物展
next week in Santa Monica and...
听着  伯特
Listen, um, Bert,
在你说出口之前  我想告诉你
before you say anything else, I...
我有男朋友了
I have a boyfriend.
这下尴尬了
This is awkward.
你以为我是邀请你跟我一起
You thought I was gonna ask you to go with me
-去看展览吗  -难道不是吗
to the mineral show. - Weren't you?
是的
Yeah.
多谢你的好意  但
That's very nice of you, but...
我的确有男朋友了
I do have a boyfriend.
你们都这么说
That's what you all say.
你们只是不想跟我出去约会
You just don't want to go out with me
因为我是个令人讨厌的人
because I have an off-putting personality.
不  不是的
No, that's not true.
我的男朋友也是一个让人讨厌的人
My boyfriend has an off-putting personality, too.
而且比你讨厌多了
Like, way worse than you.
别担心
Don't worry.
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
我这么大只  个性古怪  长相奇怪
I mean, I'm big and weird and funny-looking
从来不会有人想跟我一起玩
and no one ever wants to do anything with me.
别那样说
Don't say that.
没关系
It's okay.
我知道我就是一怪物
I know I'm a monster.
不  伯特  别走
No, Bert, come on.
我很乐意陪你去看矿物展
I'd love to go to the mineral show with you.
太棒了
Sweet.
那就算约会啦
It's a date.
才不算呢
No, it's not.
为时已晚啦
Too late!
自从那辆韩国教堂大巴
Yeah. Haven't seen this many people in my store
从我店前门玻璃撞进来后
since that Korean church bus
我店再也没有见过那么多人
crashed through my front window.
斯图尔特
Hey! Stuart!
杰西
Jesse.
好久不见
Haven't seen you in forever.
你看你都灰成这样了
Look how gray you've gotten.
我的头发一直都是这个颜色
My hair's exactly the same color as always.
不  我是在说你的肤色
No, I was talking about your skin.
我的朋友要找一本漫画书
Look, uh, my friend here needs a comic book...
她应该是无意走进你的店吧
And she went into your store by mistake.
幸好他家店没人  不会有人知道你走错地方
Good thing there was no one there to see you.
你要找什么
What do you need?
这本啊  我这里有
Oh, yeah, yeah. I got this.
就在这边
Right over here.
运动裤肥仔  连你也抛弃我
Even you, Sweatpants?
这里有免费爆米花呢
Free popcorn.
要不要来一杯咖啡
Can I offer you a coffee?
是浓缩咖啡还是拿铁呢
Espresso? Latte?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
你呢  斯图  摩卡还是司康饼
How about you, Stu? Mocha? Scone?
还是要这附近施舍处的地址啊
Directions to the nearest soup kitchen?
他知道施舍处在哪
He knows where the soup kitchen is.
在默顿大道上
It's on Merton Avenue.
我不喜欢你这样对待我的朋友
I don't think I like the way you're treating my friend.
抱歉
Sorry.
你还想不想要这本书了
You want the book or not?
想要也不买你的
Not from you.
我们走  斯图尔特
Let's go, Stuart.
你知道吗  杰西
You know something, Jesse?
虽说你生意兴隆
You may have a successful business
均衡营养
a-and the kind of pink complexion
养得一脸粉嫩
that comes with good nutrition...
但我拥有更重要的东西
...but I have something more important.
是什么
What's that?
友谊
Friendship.
但我会毫不犹豫放弃友谊来换取这一切
Which I would trade in a heartbeat for all of this.
矿物岩石展览
The mineral and rock show?
即使不跟伯特去  听着都很没劲
That would be awful even without Bert.
那我现在应该怎么办
So what am I supposed to do now?
让你的子宫为他的巨人婴儿做好准备
Prepare your uterus for his gigantic offspring?
不许拿这事开玩笑
This isn't funny.
我必须跟他说实话
I'm gonna have to tell him the truth:
就算我没有男友
that even if I didn't have a boyfriend,
也不会喜欢他
I wouldn't be interested in him.
这话我听过太多遍了
I've heard those words so many times.
琳达·诺森恰克  谭米·罗森沃塞尔
From Linda Nosenchuck, Tammy Rosenworcel...
帕德玛·卡普尔  内哈·恰德瑞
Padma Kapur, Neha Chowdury...
马茜·格罗斯曼  莉萨·马扎里诺
...Marci Grossman, Lisa Mazzarino...
-梅根·平卡斯  -谭米·周
- ...Megan Pincus... - ...Tammy Cho...
我们常去那家星巴克的女生叫什么来着
Oh, who was that girl from our Starbucks?
-艾琳·罗素  -没错  艾琳
- Arlene Russel! - Yes! Arlene!
她在我俩的卡布奇诺杯上  都写上了"不可能"
She wrote "no way" on both our cappuccinos.
可怜的伯特
Poor Bert.
有一个悲催的下午在等着他
That guy's got a rough afternoon ahead of him.
你们希望一个女生
Well, how would you want a girl
如何拒绝你们
to tell you she wasn't interested?
我希望她和我好好坐着
I guess, uh, I'd like her to sit me down,
看着我的眼睛说
look me in the eye and say,
"我错了  我爱你"
"I was wrong. I love you."
或许再用上特别的方式爱抚我
And then maybe she could touch me in a special way.
没错  拒绝男生就要这样
That's how you reject a guy.
我没时间听你俩瞎掰
Okay, I don't have time for this.
我要直接去找他  残忍地说出真相算了
I'm just gonna go find him and be brutally honest.
-别这样  -他会很伤心的
- No, don't. - He'll be so upset.
他很可能会爬上帝国大厦
He'll probably climb up the Empire State Building
像电影里的金刚一样乱拍飞机泄愤
and start swatting at planes.
要我们帮你说吗
You want us to talk to him?
可以吗
Really?
-你们愿意代劳吗  -当然
- You would do that? - Sure.
我们都曾有过这样的经历
We've both been in his shoes.
我们会让他失望的同时  感觉到同情与尊重
We'll let him down with compassion and respect.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们走
Let's go.
跟他说她是拉拉吗
So we tell him she's a lesbian, right?
当然是说她是拉拉啦
Of course we tell him she's a lesbian.
保持三
And hold three...
二  一
two... one.
非常好
Very good.
现在试试战士二式
Now let's try Warrior II.
保持
And hold.
有报道指出有些伟大的瑜伽修行者
I've read that there are great yogis
可以随心所欲掌控自己的身体
who have such mastery over their bodies
他们能通过生殖器汲水
they can draw water in through their genitals.
我们今天还不会练到这一层次
Yeah, well, I don't think we're gonna get to do that today.
太遗憾了
Too bad.
感觉用这种办法喝奶昔不错
It seems like a good way to drink a milk shake
至少大脑不会冰到痛
without getting brain freeze.
现在是反转战士式
And now we go to Reverse Warrior.
她是怎么说服你做瑜伽的
How did she get you to do yoga?
说实话  我以为她说的是"尤达"
Well, to be honest, I thought she said "Yoda."
我在帮他放松  因为他和你不同
I'm helping him relax because, unlike you,
他支持我
he supports me.
究竟要我说多少次啊
Oh, how many times do I have to say it?
我支持你
I support you.
谢尔顿  休息下
Sheldon, take a break.
合十致敬
Namaste.
如果你支持我  那通电话是什么意思
Okay, if you support me, what was with that phone call?
好吧  我不确定你是否该辞职
Fine. I'm not sure you should have quit.
但如果你这么在乎我的想法
But if you care so much what I think,
你为什么不在辞职前问我呢
why didn't you ask me before you did it?
所以现在我做事需要你的批准吗
Oh, so now I need your permission?
你在辞职前会征求我的意见吗
Would you have asked me before you quit your job?
当然会
Yes.
我觉得我们的关系已经到了
I thought we were in the kind of relationship
什么事都一起做决定的阶段
where we make decisions together.
如果我错了  那也许我们应该谈谈
If I'm wrong, then maybe we need to talk about
我们的关系究竟在哪一阶段
the kind of relationship we're actually in.
也许是需要谈谈了
Yeah, well, maybe we do.
你们想谈的话  我也很乐意谈
I'm willing to if you guys are.
给我们一些空间好吗
Can we please have some privacy?
不行
Y... No.
除了你们俩  我也是这段关系的一名成员
I'm as much a part of this relationship as you two,
我觉得是时候大家把话说开了
and I think it's high time we put all our cards on the table.
比如  这段感情的未来在哪里
Yeah. For example, where is this going?
你们到底会不会结婚
Are you two ever getting married?
还有婚后  我们仨要住在哪里
And, if so, where will we all live?
你们有考虑这个问题吗
Have you thought about that?
-没有  -佩妮呢
- No. - Penny?
慢着  我们这是在干嘛
Okay, wait. What are we doing?
不知为何  我们现在谈的是
For some reason, we're planning a future
我们与谢尔顿永远住在一起的未来
where we both live with Sheldon forever.
很好  总算有点进展了
Good. Now we're getting somewhere.
我知道你觉得我太过鲁莽
Look, I know you think I'm being reckless,
也许你是对的
and you might be right,
但我需要把握这次机会
but I need to take this shot.
对  这是说真的
Yeah, no kidding.
尽管她在简历上造假
Despite what it says on her resume,
她早就不是22岁了
she is no longer 22.
我发誓  我向来支持你
I swear, I am on your side.
你总是口头上说支持我
You keep saying you're on my side,
-而你的言行完全不一致  -他对我也是这样
- but you don't act like it. - He does that to me, too.
我们为什么要容忍你这种行为
Why do we put up with it?
听我说  我永远做不到你现在做的事
Listen, I could never do what you're doing, okay?
我没这么大胆
I would be terrified.
其实我心里也很害怕
Well, it's scary for me, too.
我还好啦
I'm fine with it.
我的意思是  不能因为我做不到
My point is, just because I couldn't do it
就代表你不应该去做
doesn't mean you shouldn't.
我为你骄傲
And I'm proud of you.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
为了庆祝重归于好
Well, to celebrate this reconciliation,
咱们分享一杯奶昔吧
let's all share a milk shake.
佩妮  你用吸管  我们"龙汲水"
Uh, Penny, you'll need a straw.
-你还是回来了  -是的
- You're back. - Yes, I am!
我还有一些话要对你说
There's a few more things I want to say to you.
斯图尔特的店挺好的
Stuart's store is just fine,
而且他人也比你好多了
and he's a much nicer person than you are,
如果那本漫画书还在
and if you still have that comic,
我现在就想买
I'd like to buy it right now!
没问题
No problem.
等的时候要来杯拿铁吗
Oh, you want a latte while you wait?
不  我才不要拿铁
No, I don't want a latte!
我要卡布奇诺和蓝莓司康饼
I want a cappuccino and a blueberry scone!
我这里只有巧克力曲奇饼
I only have chocolate chip.
这更符合姐心意
Well, that sounds even better!
多谢你们陪我去看矿物岩石展
Thanks for coming to the mineral and rock show with me.
很抱歉艾米不想去
We're sorry Amy didn't want to go.
我们真的深感抱歉[后悔]
Really, really sorry.
有你们陪我  还要她干嘛
Who needs her when I have you guys?
岩石展览
Rock show!
岩石展览  岩石展览
Rock show! Rock show!
岩石展览
Rock show!
Rock show...!